Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Studio Series III (Box 8)
  - A group portrait of several adults in a classroom., 14 November 1974; ref1004; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Women; Men; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of several women, one man, and two boys., 30 August 1972; ref1005; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Women; Men; Boys; Children; Tents; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman., 5 January 1975; ref1006; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Women; Jewelry; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of a crowd (linked ref1008, 1009)., 12 June 1974; ref1007; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Crowds; Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of a crowd (linked ref1007, 1009)., 12 June 1974; ref1008; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Crowds; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Regional/National Dress; Uniforms; Aleppo, Syria; Crowds; Men; Women
  - A group portrait of a crowd (linked ref1007, 1008)., 12 June 1974; ref1009; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Crowds; Aleppo, Syria; Uniforms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - A group portrait of several women sitting., 10 October 1976; ref1010; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Women; Boys; Children; Aleppo, Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several men sitting at a table and smoking., 10 October 1976; ref1011; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Smoking; Cigarettes; Men; Drinks/Beverages; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Aleppo, Syria
  - A portrait of a man playing violin., Circa 1970-1980; ref1012; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Violins; String Instruments; Musical Instruments; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Musicians
  - A group picture of two women walking., 30 August 1972; ref1013; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Women; Cars/Trucks; Streets/Roads; Bags/Purses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of several women and men dressed up., 25 March 1971; ref1014; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Women; Men; Cigarettes; Smoking; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Events/Occasions; Aleppo, Syria
  - group portrait of a woman and three men, two of them are shaking hands., 29 October 1963; ref1015; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Women; Events/Occasions; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of three men talking., 14 March 1962; ref1016; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Aleppo, Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several men at a table., 10 October 1976; ref1017; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Facial Hair; Drinks/Beverages; Aleppo, Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of two men and two women., 10 February 1962; ref1018; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of three men, and two women shaking hands., Circa 1960-1980; ref1019; Studio Al Ahram, Aleppo, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Men; Women; Bags/Purses; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of three men hugging two women., Circa 1965-1980; ref1020; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Women; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Weddings; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Events/Occasions
  - A group picture of a woman drinking next to a man., Circa 1965-1980; ref1021; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Food; Jewelry; Events/Occasions; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Group Portraits; Drinks/Beverages
  - A group portrait of a woman linking arms with a man wearing glasses., Circa 1965-1980; ref1022; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Syria; Weddings; Events/Occasions; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Drinks/Beverages; Men; Women
  - A group portrait of several people toasting., Circa 1965-1980; ref1023; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Events/Occasions; Drinks/Beverages; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people dancing in a line., Circa 1965-1980; ref1024; Studio Adib, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Women; Dancing; Events/Occasions; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of several men and two women dancing in a circle., Circa 1965-1980; ref1025; Studio Adib, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Dancing; Events/Occasions; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of several men and women at a table., Circa 1965-1980; ref1026; Studio Safar & Vartan, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.8 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions; Men; Women; Bags/Purses; Smoking
  - A group portrait of two men talking to a woman., Circa 1965-1980; ref1027; Studio Safar & Vartan, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.8 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Drinks/Beverages; Events/Occasions; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman dancing in a crowd., Circa 1965-1980; ref1028; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 12.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dancing; Women; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Events/Occasions
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman dancing in a crowd., Circa 1965-1980; ref1029; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.7 x 12.6 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Dancing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of a crowd of men and women., Circa 1965-1980; ref1030; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.7 x 12.7 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Dancing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Events/Occasions
  - A group portrait of a two men and two women drinking from a boot-shaped glass (linked ref1032, 1033, 1034)., Circa 1965-1980; ref1031; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Alcohol; Drinks/Beverages; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of a man holding a baby (linked ref1031, 1033, 1034)., Circa 1965-1980; ref1032; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.1 x 12.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Children; Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of three men drinking from a boot-shaped glass (linked ref1031, 1032, 1034)., Circa 1965-1980; ref1033; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Men; Alcohol; Drinks/Beverages; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of four men and a woman posing (linked ref1031, 1032, 1033)., Circa 1965-1980; ref1034; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.1 x 12.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A group portrait of several men, women, and children., Circa 1965-1980; ref1035; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Children; Uniforms
  - A portrait of a man sitting on a car., Circa 1960-1980; ref1036; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.6 x 12.6 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Men; Cars/Trucks; Architecture; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of several men and women outdoors., May 1970; ref1037; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Men; Women; Children; Nuns; Religion; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a person's eyes., 23 October 1961; ref1038; Studio Jacques, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 19.1 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of two girls in uniform, one is aiming a shotgun (linked ref1040, 1041)., Circa 1960-1975; ref1039; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Girls; Outdoors; Weapons; Guns; Uniforms; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of two girls in uniform, one is aiming a shotgun (linked ref1039, 1041)., Circa 1960-1975; ref1040; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Girls; Outdoors; Weapons; Guns; Children; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of a girl in uniform aiming a shotgun (linked ref1039, 1040)., Circa 1960-1975; ref1041; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Girls; Children; Syria; Uniforms; Guns; Weapons; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of two women sitting on a curb., Circa 1965-1980; ref1042; Studio Al Assime, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Women; Bags/Purses; Fountains; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of several men and boys, one man is wearing a uniform., Circa 1955-1980; ref1043; Studio Umaya, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18 x 13.2 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Men; Boys; Uniforms; Crowds; Group Portraits; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a panel of men and women (linked ref1045)., Circa 1970-1980; ref1044; Studio Safar & Vartan, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.8 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of a panel of men and women (linked ref1044)., Circa 1970-1980; ref1045; Studio Safar & Vartan, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.8 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A group portrait of a man and woman shaking hands., Circa 1970-1980; ref1046; Studio Safar & Vartan, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.8 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several women getting food., 7 October 1969; ref1047; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Women; Food; Events/Occasions; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of a married couple driving away., 15 August 1964; ref1048; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Weddings; Men; Women; Cars/Trucks; Events/Occasions; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Group Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a man., Circa 1950-1970; ref1049; Studio Nabil, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6.2 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of three men walking on a road., 24 October 1970; ref1050; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Cars/Trucks; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a uniform., Circa 1950-1970; ref1051; Photo Ardo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.3 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Boys; Children; Uniforms
  - A studio portrait of a girl wearing a dress., Circa 1950-1970; ref1052; Photo Ardo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.6 x 8.5 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Girls; Jewelry; Children; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a woman., Circa 1950-1970; ref1053; Photo Michel, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.5 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Women; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1951; ref1054; Photo Katchadour, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.2 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Boys; Children; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man and a woman., Circa 1950-1970; ref1055; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 8.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Women; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of five boys, a woman, and a man., 9 September 1951; ref1056; Photo Nofal, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.1 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Men; Women; Children; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; French Writing; Syria
  - A group portrait of two girls wearing veils and a boy., Circa 1955-1970; ref1057; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 8.7 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Flags; Boys; Girls; Children
  - A studio portrait of a child., Circa 1955-1970; ref1058; Studio Dikran, Damascus, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 8.3 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Children; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a baby wearing a cross., 3 March 1967; ref1059; Studio Echbelia, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Children; Religion; Religious Crosses; Art; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria
  - A portrait of a girl wearing a veil and holding a Bible., Circa 1955-1970; ref1060; Photo V. Derounian, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Aleppo, Syria; Head Covers/Veils; Books; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Girls; Children
  - A group portrait of a girl dressed as an angel and a girl wearing a veil., Circa 1955-1970; ref1061; Photo Ardo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Girls; Head Covers/Veils; Costumes; Religion; Religious Crosses; Children; Furnishings; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a girl., Circa 1950-1970; ref1062; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 16.8 x 11.7 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Damascus, Syria; Girls; Children; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of two women and two children., Circa 1950-1970; ref1063; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 12.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Women; Children; Girls; Balloons; Damascus, Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several men, women, and children at a party., Circa 1950-1970; ref1064; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Children; Boys; Girls; Birthdays; Events/Occasions; Food; Balloons; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a girl., Circa 1950-1970; ref1065; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Girls; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Children
  - A group portrait of a priest and a monk giving Communion to three boys (linked ref1067)., Circa 1950-1970; ref1066; 1 Photographic Prints; 21.7 x 16.3 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Men; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Children; Religion; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of a priest and a monk giving Communion to three boys (linked ref1066)., Circa 1950-1970; ref1067; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.4 x 17.7 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Men; Boys; Religion; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of several men and women., 15 October 1959; ref1068; Photo Azad, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Damascus, Syria; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several men and three women in front of a chalk board., Circa 1950-1970; ref1069; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Schools/Education; Mathematics; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Damascus, Syria
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1071, 1072, 1073, 1074, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1070; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Aleppo, Syria; Women; Costumes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1072, 1073, 1074, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1071; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Women; Aleppo, Syria; Costumes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1071, 1073, 1074, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1072; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Aleppo, Syria; Women; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1071, 1072, 1074, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1073; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1071, 1072, 1073, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1074; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1071, 1072, 1073, 1074)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1075; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Wedding Portrait Series (Box 6)
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., December 23 1962; ref1277; Tirage Photo Dadour, Alep (Aleppo, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 23.5 x 17.5 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Armenian Writing; Aleppo, Syria; Jewelry; Head Covers/Veils; Weddings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Women
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., 1963; ref1278; Tirage Photo Dadour, Alep (Aleppo, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 23.5 x 17.5 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Weddings; Head Covers/Veils; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Men; Women; English Writing
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., Circa 1960-1970; ref1279; Photo Kevork, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.5 x 13.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Weddings; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., Circa 1960-1970; ref1280; Photo Kevork, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.5 x 13.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils; Weddings
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., Circa 1960-1970; ref1281; Photo Kevork, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.5 x 13.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Men; Women; Weddings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Syria